SEIF AMR

WEB DEVELOPER

- **1** +201128444403
- ✓ seifammar1125@gmail.com
- Meliopolis, Cairo, Egypt

SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- Sass
- TailwindCss
- JavaScript
- Vueis
- Laravel
- Wordpress
- Knowledge (UI/UX principles)
- git
- knowledge of ReactJs , React native
- Java

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF INFORMATICS AND COMPUTER SCIENCES

The British university in Egypt

2018 - 2014

PROFILE

4 years as a software developer seeks for joining teams as a Software developer providing Software solution which meets costumer needs in addition to ability to take a new development challenges and new technologies and tools Moreover Have the ability to work with teams and groups which translate UI/UX design wireframes to well designed ,Reusable and clean code.

EXPERIENCE

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

mar 2021 - Present

34 Media Labs

- Transforming wireframes and ui designs to fully clean reusable and funcional code
- build,test and maintain webapps and websites
- participate in Apis design and documentation
- · fixing bugs and code revamping

TECHNICAL BUISSNESS ANALYST

jan 2021 - mar 2021

tanmeyah for microfinance services

- · gather requirements from stakeholders
- · ensure projects technical feasability
- · collaborating in technical actions

DESKTOP DEVELOPER

jun 2018 - jul 2019

Gratsia Tours

 Building and maintaining desktop application for managing reservations and financials

PROJECTS

FITZROY-WEATHER

HTTPS://GITHUB.COM/SEIF1125/FITZROY-WEATHER

A REACT.JS WEB APP WHICH GETS THE WEATHER DETAILS USING OPENWEATHERMAP API

NEW AVENUE

HTTPS://NEWAVENUE-EGYPT.COM

HELPING CLIENTS FIND THE PERFECT HOME FOR THE PERFECT FIT THAT MEETS THEIR NEEDS TO FIND THE BEST DEALS FOR OUR CLIENTS, WITH THE OPTIMAL PAYMENT PLANS.

RAHET BALY

HTTPS://RAHETBALLY.COM

A VUE WEBAPP DESIGNED TO BE A FULL-FLEDGED SUPPORT PLATFORM FOR NEW MOTHERS. WE SUPPORT MOMS THROUGH A HUGE ARRAY OF PRODUCTS & SERVICES THAT MAKES THEIR LIVES EASIER, HEALTHIER & HAPPIER.